Finding Aid of the Midwest Archives Conference Records, 1972-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1972-2014, UWM Manuscript Collection 194; 42.1 cubic ft. (112 boxes) 1,083 digital files (171 MB)
  - 1. President, 1972-2013
    - Valerie Gerrard Browne
      - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - New Author Award, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - NHPRC, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Nominating Committee and Tellers Subcommittee, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - NUCMC, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Planning Retreat, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - President's Award, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1991, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - Fall 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1993, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - Spring 1991, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1992, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1992, 20th Anniversary Luncheon, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - Spring 1992, Raiders of the Lost Archives Reprise, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
        - Spring 1992, "Wither MAC" Study Discussion Groups, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 14)
        - Spring 1993, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Program Innovation Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Public Information Officer, 1991-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Russian Archive Seminar, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Secretary, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Secretary/Treasurer, Split of Office, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Treasurer, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Vice President, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Frank Cook
      - Appointments, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Archival Issues Editorial Board, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Archives Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Business Meetings, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Calendar Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Chicago Hotel, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Constitution and Bylaws Revision, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Council, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Council Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
      - Council Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
      - Development Coordinator/Vendor Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Education Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1993, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Fall 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - Fall 1995, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1996, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1997, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - Fall 1998, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - Spring 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - MAC Newsletter Editorial Board, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Meeting Coordinating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Membership Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - National Coordinating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Nominating Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Paid Services, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - President's Award, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Prez Sez Letters, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1993, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1994, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Program Innovation Fund (PIF) Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Public Information Officer, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Publications Planning Task Force, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - SAA Committee on Regional Archival Activity, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Scholarships, 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Treasurer, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Mark Greene
      - Anniversary Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Annual Business Meeting, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Archival Issues Editorial Board, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Archivist of the United States, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Calendar, 1994-1996 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Committee Appointments, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Council, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 8-11)
      - Council, Cuban Archivist, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Council, Memorial Scholarship, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Council, Minority Scholarship Endowment, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Council, Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Development Coordinator, Vendor Relations, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Distinguished Service Award, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Education Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Emeritus Member, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Guidelines, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Local Arrangements Committee
        - Fall 1995, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1996, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Meeting Coordinating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Meeting, Fall 1998, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Membership Committee, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference, 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Newsletter Editorial Board, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Nominating Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - President's Award, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Program Committee
        - Fall 1995, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Fall 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Spring 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Spring 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Program Innovation Fund (PIF), 1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Public Information Officer, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Scholarships for Minority Students, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Teller Committee, 1996-1007 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Treasurer, 1992-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Pat Michaelis
      - Advocacy Committee, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Archival Issues Editorial Board, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 1994-1997 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Chicago Hotel, 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1994, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Council, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
      - Council, Committee Guidelines, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Council, SAA Workshops, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Development Coordinator, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Education Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Insurance, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - International Initiative, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Joint MAC/MARAC Membership, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Coordinating Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Meeting, Fall 2000, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Meeting Manual, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Meeting Planning, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Meetings, 1997-1999 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Membership Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - National Coordinating Committee, 1997-1999 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - New Member Statistics, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Newsletter Editor, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - NHPRC, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Nominating Committee, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Paid Services, 1995-1999 (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - President's Award Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - President's Lunch, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Program Committee, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Scholarship Committees, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Twenty-fifth Anniversary Year, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Frank Boles
      - Advocacy Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Calendar, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 31, Folder 3-9)
      - Correspondence, Email, 1999-2001
      - Council, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
      - Development Coordinator, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Guidelines, 1999, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Insurance, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - MAC Agenda, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - MAC/MARAC, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Meeting
        - Fall 1998, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1999, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Fall 2000, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Fall 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Fall 2002, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Spring 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Spring 2001, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Meeting Manual, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Minority Scholarship, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - President's Award, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Website, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Cheri Thies
      - Advertising Rate Task Force, 2002 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Business Meeting, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Council Meeting, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - Insurance Study, 2001-2002 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - International Initiative, 2001-2003 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Steve McShane
      - A*Census, 2003-2004 (Box 113, Folder 6)
      - Business Meeting, 2004 (Box 113, Folder 7)
      - Calendar Committee, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      - Council Meeting, 2004-2006 (Box 113, Folder 9-11)
      - International Initiative, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - Issues Task Force, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - Kentucky Proposal, 2004-2005 (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - Letter to Washington DC Archives, 2003-2004 (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - Membership Database Task Force, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - RoweCom, 2003 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Elisabeth Wittman
      - Archival Issues Editorial Board, 2003-2008 (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - Council Meeting, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 19-20)
      - Members Meeting, 2005 (Box 113, Folder 21)
      - Newsletter, 2003-2007 (Box 113, Folder 22)
      - President's Award, 2004-2007 (Box 113, Folder 23)
      - Public Information Officer, 2002-2006 (Box 113, Folder 24)
      - "The State of MAC," 2007 (Box 115, Folder 22`)
      - Strategic Planning Meeting, 2005-2007 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - Vendor Relations, 2003-2007 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      - Webmaster, 2005-2007 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Dennis Meissner
      - Council Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Development Coordinator, 2005-2008 (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - Guidelines Revisions, 2007-2009 (Box 115, Folder 18)
      - Nominating Committee, 2006-2010 (Box 114, Folder 6)
      - Website Revisions, 2007-2008 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Tanya Zanish-Belcher
    - Ellen Swain
      - Advocacy, undated
      - Archival Issues, undated
      - Constitution Bylaws Review, 2011
      - Development Task Force, 2012
      - Documentation Working Group, 2013
      - Education Committee, undated
      - Financial Advisory Committee, undated
      - Fortieth Anniversary Campaign, 2011-2012
      - Newsletter Redesign Task Force, 2012
      - Online Publications Task Force, 2012
      - Presidents Letters, 2011-2013
      - Presidents Reports, 2011-2012
      - SAA Regional Forum and Planning Committee, undated
      - Values Statement, 2013
  - 2. Vice Presidents, 1996-2011
    This record subgroup contains the files of MAC vice presidents. Prior to 1994, the vice president had limited responsbilities, which likely explains the absence of archival records from that period. In 1994, Council assigned the vice president responsibilities for serving as liaison and advisor to the program and local arrangements committees, and succeeding to the office of president should it be vacated. Researchers will find documentation relating to these topics in this subgroup.
    - Elisabeth Wittman
      - Appointments, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Education Committee, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Local Arrangements Committee, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 9)
      - Meeting Coordinating Committee, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Meeting Manual, 1997 (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - Membership Committee, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 12)
      - Program Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 114, Folder 13-14)
      - Reports, 2005 (Box 114, Folder 15)
      - Webpage, 1996 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Sherry Williams
      - Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Paul Eisloeffel
      - Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Tanya Zanish-Belcher
      - Fall Symposium, 2006-2007 (Box 114, Folder 19-20)
      - Program Workshop Development, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - Local Arrangements Committee Reports, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - Newsletter Columns, 2006-2007
      - Reports
        - 2006-2008 (Box 115, Folder 3)
        - 2006-2008
      - Spring Meeting, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Doug Bicknese
      - Fall Symposium, 2010 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - MAC Logos, 2007
      - Meeting Manual Revisions, 2008
      - Meeting Proposal, 2011 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Special Meeting Committees and Task Forces, undated
      - Spring Meeting, 2010 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - Symposium Development, 2007
      - Vice President Publications, 2008-2010
    - Mark Shelstad
      - Education Survey, undated
      - MAC Fortieth Anniversary, 2011-2012
      - Vice Presidents Newsletter, 2010-2012
  - 3. Secretary and Treasurer, 1972-2013
    - A. Secretary and Treasurer, 1972-1990
      This record subgroup contains records from both the Secretary and Treasurer prior to when the roles were split in 1991. Included are articles of incorporation, committee guidelines, constitution and bylaws, correspondence, financial reports, bi-annual meeting materials, and membership data, directories, and surveys.
      - Archives and Society Task Force, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Archives Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Articles of Incorporation, 1972-1976 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Certification Survey, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Committee Guidelines
        - 1978, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Revisions, 1983-1989 (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
      - Computerization Study, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Conservation Committee, 1977-1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1972, 1979, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, Revision Committee, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence
        - 1972-1977 (Box 33, Folder 21-22)
        - 1978-1990 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
        - Officers and Council, 1979-1989 (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
      - Development Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Education Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Emeritus Membership Award, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, Guidelines, 1977-1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Financial Planning and Reports Data, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Financial Records, 1972-1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Financial Resources Study, 1981-1989 (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
      - Governing Structures Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Grant Projects, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Insurance Task Force, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Iowa Archives, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Local Arrangements Committee Guidelines, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Logo, 1988, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - MAC Newsletter, 1980-1988 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Mailing List, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Meeting
        - Fall 1972, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Fall 1973, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Fall 1974, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Fall 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Fall 1976, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Fall 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Fall 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Fall 1980, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Fall 1981, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Fall 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - Fall 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Fall 1985, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - Fall 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - Fall 1987, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Fall 1987, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - Fall 1988, 1986-1989 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - Fall 1989, 1985-1989 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Fall 1991, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - Fall 1993, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - Spring 1972, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Spring 1973, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Spring 1974, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Spring 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - Spring 1976, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - Spring 1977, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - Spring 1978, 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Spring 1980, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Spring 1981, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Spring 1983, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Spring 1984, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - Spring 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - Spring 1986, 1986-1987 (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - Spring 1987, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Spring 1988, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - Spring 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Membership Brochure, 1984, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Membership Data and Mailing Lists, 1972-1976 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Membership Data Base Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Membership Development Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Membership Directory, 1972-1978 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Membership Directory, 1981-1988 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Membership, New Members, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Membership Questionnaire, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Membership Questionnaire, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Membership Survey, 1972-1981 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Membership Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Midwestern Archivist, 1978-1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Midwestern Archivist, NEH Grant for Publication of Networks Issue, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Minutes, Analysis, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - NHPRC Grant, 1985-1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Nominating Committee, 1979-1992 (Box 42, Folder 4-6)
      - Nominating Committee Guidelines, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Nominating/Tellers Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Officers and Council, 1979, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - President's Award Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Proclamation, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Professional Rights and Responsibilities Statement, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Program Analysis Committee and Education Committee, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Program Committee Guidelines, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Program Questionnaire, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Public Information Officer, 1987-1989 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Reports, 1981-1989 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - SAA, 1972-1981 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - SAA, MAC Mixer, 1984-1988 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1983-1989 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Subject Access Seminar, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Surveys and Questionnaires, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - University Microfilms International (UMI), 1980-1992 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - B. Secretary, 1982-2013
      This record subgroup contains records from the Secretary, primarily after the roles of the Secretary and Treasurer were split in 1991. Included are award, commitee, and correspondence files, a MAC chronology, and membership directories and membership statistics.
      - Abbey Publications, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Advertising Policies and Rates, 1992-1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Automation Task Force, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Awards, 1990-1994 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Certificate of Insurance, 1993-1997 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Contributions, National Coordinating Committee (NCC), 1994 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence
        - 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - 1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Distinguished Service Award, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - "Do You Have Archival Issues?" Cartoon Copyright Agreement, 2012 (Box 115, Folder 16)
      - Emeritus Membership Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Guidelines, 1992, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Logos, 2005
      - MAC Chronology, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Mailing List, Sale of, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Manual, 1994-1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Member Interest Survey, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Membership Committee, 1982-1992 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Membership Directory, 1990-2002 (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
      - Membership Statistics from 1974 to 1991, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Membership Survey, 2008 (Box 115, Folder 12)
      - National Coordinating Committee for the Promotion of History, 1985-1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - New England Archivists, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Paid Services Task Force, 1993-1995 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - President's Award, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Program Innovation Fund (PIF), 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Program Innovation Fund (PIF)
        - Minority Scholarships, 1993-1995 (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - New Author's Award, 1992-1994 (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Third World Archives, 1991-1993 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Workshop Curricular Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Secretary Manual and Information, 2013
      - Secretary's Reports, 2003-2007 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - Secretary-Treasurer's Office, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Society of Southwest Archivists (SSA), 1989-1991 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Strategic Planning, 2010 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - C. Treasurer, 1994-2008
      This record subgroup contains records from the Treasurer after the roles of the Secretary and Treasurer were split.
      - Budget, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Finances, 1998-2000 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Financial Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Financial Statements, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Treasurer's Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - 4. Council, 1972-2013
    This record subgroup contains Council meeting materials, including minutes and materials discussed at the meetings. Records document the work of numerous committees and includes committee guidelines and reports, particularly reports regarding the planning of the bi-annual meetings. Included are financial reports, new member statistics, and editorial reports relating to the newsletter and the journal. Files also document issues of concern to the profession.
    - Between-Meeting Council Items, 2009-2013
    - Council Meetings, 1972-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1-7)
    - Council Meetings, 1980-1982 (Box 44, Folder 1-5)
    - Council Meetings, 1983-1986 (Box 45, Folder 1-4)
    - Council Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 1-7)
    - Council Meetings, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 1-8)
    - Council Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1-6)
    - Council Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1-6)